Guide to the Dairy Farm Business Summary and Analysis Project records, 1947-2005.
Dairy Farm Business Summary and Analysis Project records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Dairy Farm Business Summary and Analysis Project records, 1947-2005.
21-43-3764
Dept. of Applied Economics and Management.Dairy Farm Business Summary and Analysis Project.
19 cubic feet.
Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes county business record summaries for dairy, grape, poultry and beef farms.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes county business record summaries for dairy, grape, poultry and beef farms.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Dept. of Applied Economics and Management.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences.Dept. of Applied Economics and Management.
Subjects:
Dairy farms--New York (State); Dairy farming--Economic aspects--New York (State).; Dairy products industry--New York (State); Dairying--New York (State)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Business Records, Account Projects, Account Summaries: Jefferson, Yates County; Farm Management Project: St. Lawrence, Lewis, Jefferson County; Wyoming County Potato Account, 1947-1948, 1958, 1964-1967 (Box 1)
- Business Records, 1955 and earlier, 1956-1959 (Box 2)
- Business Records, 1959-1962 (Box 3)
- Business Records; Oren Burbank's Study of Dutchess County Farm Management Program, 1955-1957, 1963, 1977-1980 (Box 4)
- Business Records, 1980-1982 (Box 5)
- Business Records, 1983-1984 (Box 6)
- Business Records; Regional Business Summary, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
- Business Records; Regional Business Summary, 1986-1988 (Box 8)
- Business Records; Regional Business Summary, 1988-1990 (Box 9)
- Business Records, 1990-1991 (Box 10)
- Business Records; Regional Business Summary, 1991-1993 (Box 11)
- Business Records, 1993-1994 (Box 12)
- Business Records, 1994-1996 (Box 13)
- Business Records, 1996-1997 (Box 14)
- Business Records; Financial Statements, 1998-1999 (Box 15)
- Business Records, 2000-2001 (Box 16)
- Business Records, 2001-2002 (Box 17)
- Business Records, 2004-2005 (Box 18)
- Business Records, 1957-1970, 1972-1976 (Box 19)